[
  {"question":"Replacing string from left hand side is known as",
    "answer1":"Slicing",
    "answer2":"Dicing",
    "answer3":"Trailing",
    "answer4":"Leading",
    "correct":"4",
    "score":"30"
  }
,{"question":"A function that capitalizes first letter of each word in a string, is a",
  "answer1":"strtupper ( ) function",
  "answer2":"strword ( ) function",
  "answer3":"unwords ( ) function",
  "answer4":"ucfirst ( ) function",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":"Case functions are used for",
  "answer1":"Changing lowercase to uppercase",
  "answer2":"Changing the length of string",
  "answer3":"String replacement functions",
  "answer4":"Searching functions",
  "correct":"1",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":"Chop ( ), ltrim ( ) and trim functions are used for",
  "answer1":"Slicing",
  "answer2":"Dicing",
  "answer3":"Cleaning up untidy strings",
  "answer4":"Concatenation of strings",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"30"
},
  {"question":" Which function is identical to Strstr ( )?",
    "answer1":"Strlen ( )",
    "answer2":"Strchar ( )",
    "answer3":"Strcmp ( )",
    "answer4":"None of them",
    "correct":"2",
    "score":"30"
  }
,{"question":"Selecting a substring by numerical position is property of",
  "answer1":"Strstr ( )",
  "answer2":"Substr ( )",
  "answer3":"str ( )",
  "answer4":"Strsub ( )",
  "correct":"4",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":"In substring selection which function modifies a string?",
  "answer1":"Strchar ( )",
  "answer2":"Slicing",
  "answer3":"Dicing",
  "answer4":"None of them",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":"Which function is used for escaping quotation marks, double quotation marks, backslashes and Nulls from a string?",
  "answer1":"remove ( )",
  "answer2":"removeslash( )",
  "answer3":"addslashes ( )",
  "answer4":"None of them",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":"Which function returns resulting string as its value?",
  "answer1":"scanf ( ) function",
  "answer2":"sprintf ( ) function",
  "answer3":"None of them",
  "answer4":"printf ( ) function",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"30"
},{"question":"Which two functions are used for replacing a string with another string?",
  "answer1":"Str_replace ( )",
  "answer2":"Substr_replace ( )",
  "answer3":"Replace ( )",
  "answer4":"Both A and B",
  "correct":"4",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":"Which string type is interpreted as a number of sequences and automatically interpolates variable values?",
  "answer1":"Single quoted string",
  "answer2":"Doubly quoted string",
  "answer3":"Numbered string",
  "answer4":"Both A and B",
  "correct":"2",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":"Which function is used for capitalizing first letter of a string?",
  "answer1":"strtlower ( )",
  "answer2":"strtupper ( )",
  "answer3":"ucfirst ( )",
  "answer4":"lfirst ( )",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":" In substring selection what's mean of Slicing?",
  "answer1":"Concatenating",
  "answer2":"Choosing a portion of a string",
  "answer3":"Modifying a string",
  "answer4":"Comparing a string",
  "correct":"2",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":"Concatenating operator is used for",
  "answer1":"Combining two strings",
  "answer2":"Comparing two strings",
  "answer3":"Arrays concatenation",
  "answer4":"None of them",
  "correct":"1",
  "score":"30"
},{"question":"Returns a string argument with both leading and trailing whitespace removed, is a behavior of",
  "answer1":"chop ( )",
  "answer2":"rtrim ( )",
  "answer3":"trim ( )",
  "answer4":"ltrim ( )",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"30"
},
  {"question":"By first constructing a message string and then shipping it off to receiving program, is a way of communication between PHP and",
    "answer1":"Database servers",
    "answer2":"LDAP servers",
    "answer3":"Sockets",
    "answer4":"All of them",
    "correct":"4",
    "score":"30"
  }
,{"question":"For creating pages that contain HTML forms and have multiline strings we can use",
  "answer1":"Assignment concatenation syntax",
  "answer2":"Heredoc syntax",
  "answer3":"Concatenation syntax",
  "answer4":"None of them",
  "correct":"2",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":"To use proxy server, client must be configured to access proxy instead of the",
  "answer1":"Proxy Server",
  "answer2":"Target Server",
  "answer3":"Domain Server",
  "answer4":"Original Server",
  "correct":"2",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":"  What does trailing means in replacement of functions?",
  "answer1":"Replacing string from right hand side",
  "answer2":"Replacing string from left hand side",
  "answer3":"Replacing string from middle",
  "answer4":"None of them",
  "correct":"1",
  "score":"30"
},{"question":"Literal string specified in PHP code by",
  "answer1":"Single quotation mark",
  "answer2":"Double Quotation mark",
  "answer3":"Single dollar sign",
  "answer4":"Both A and B",
  "correct":"4",
  "score":"30"
},{"question":"Which function start its search from backward rather than from beginning?",
  "answer1":"Strcmp ( )",
  "answer2":"Strstr ( )",
  "answer3":"Strpos ( )",
  "answer4":"All of them",
  "correct":"3",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":" Which function takes a single string and returns its length as an integer?",
  "answer1":"Strpos ( )",
  "answer2":"Strcmp ( )",
  "answer3":"strstr ( )",
  "answer4":"Strlen ( ",
  "correct":"4",
  "score":"30"
}
,{"question":"Strtupper ( ) function returns",
  "answer1":"All uppercase string",
  "answer2":"All lowercase string",
  "answer3":"First letter capitalized",
  "answer4":"None of them",
  "correct":"1",
  "score":"30"
}
,
  {"question":"PHP offers printf ( ) and",
    "answer1":"printh ( ) function",
    "answer2":"sprintf ( ) function",
    "answer3":"scanf ( ) function",
    "answer4":"All of them",
    "correct":"2",
    "score":"30"
  }

]